(Leonard:)Sheldon.
I didn't say "fun" fact.
I'm not a monster.
(Bernadette:)He's gonna be okay.
(all sighing)
(Sheldon:)Now it's a fun fact.
(Stuart:)Boy, stuff like this really
puts things in perspective.
(Penny:)Why are you
dressed like that?
(Stuart:)Oh, uh, Howard thought
it'd be funny
(Stuart:)to tell me
it was a costume party.
(Bernadette:)That wasn't nice.
(Stuart:)No, but he almost died,
so we're cool.
(Raj:)You know, if you think about it,
tonight was kind of like
(Raj:)a real-life
Game of Thrones.
(Amy:)How?
(Raj:)Well, Howard eating
that pistachio
(Raj:)was like when King
Joffrey got poisoned.
(Penny:)Okay, well, that was murder,
this was an accident.
(Raj:)Okay.
(Raj:)But you using Sheldon
(Raj:)to do your dirty work
is like when Cersei
(Raj:)used the King's Guard
to do her bidding.
(Sheldon:)Cersei uses her body
to manipulate men.
(Sheldon:)Penny just takes me
to The LEGO Store.
(Raj:)Okay. Oh, how about this?